sweepstakesmama.com 2011-11-09

# Sweepstakes Mama: Privacy Statement

****  
Your privacy is important to Sweepstakes Mama.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Sweepstakes Mama may collect, and the ways in which Sweepstakes Mama uses that personal information.

**Comment Policy:**   
**I reserve the right to edit and delete any comments.** Any comments that I consider are spam, offensive in nature or not family-friendly I will delete.

****  
**Personal information collection**  
For specific purposes, Sweepstakes Mama may audit and collect some forms of your personal information for a variety of uses. Examples of such is as follows.

  * information about how to contact you and about your use of this website This includes but is not limited to your  name and email address

  * Any information you provide while registering or commenting on Sweepstakes Mama. This includes your name and email address.

  * Any information you provide for the use of subscribing to posts, email newsletters, etc for the purpose of gaining more information from Sweepstakes Mama or that Sweepstakes Mama may use to gain demographics information.

  * I reserve to use any other information that you send to Sweepstakes Mama for similar uses.

**How I may use your personal information**  
Sweepstakes Mama may use your personal information to adequately administer this website, personalize the website for her readers, or publish information about her readers on the website.

Where Sweepstakes Mama discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of **this** privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Sweepstakes Mama may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend the legal rights of Sweepstakes Mama and its writers. Sweepstakes Mama will not share will take reasonable precautions in keeping your personal information secure so that it is not misused. Information posted on this site is shared world-wide.

****  
**Privacy Statement Updates**  
****Sweepstakes Mama may update this privacy statement at any time and it is her readers responsibility to check it periodically to be aware of any updates. This privacy statement may change without notification.

**Other websites**  
Sweepstakes Mama may have links to other sites for the purpose of advertising or for promotional reasons. Third-Party advertisers are present on this site to serve ads when readers visit Sweepstakes Mama. They may collect information from this site including but not limited to your name, address, email address, phone number or other information about your visits in order to provide you goods and services specific to your interests. If you would like to more know about this practice, how your information is used, and the options involved limiting these companies use of your information visit this site <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>  
Sweepstakes Mama is not in any way responsible for other companies or advertisers use of your information, their privacy policies, or any use of your information they gain while you visit Sweepstakes Mama. 

**Contact Sweepstakes Mama  
**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Sweepstakes Mama's treatment of your personal information, please contact Sweepstakes Mama by email at [sweepstakesmama@rocketmail.com](mailto:sweepstakesmama@rocketmail.com)
